allegiancemusical.com 2015-09-06

# Privacy Policy - Allegiance

### Privacy Policy and Legal Notice

We have created this Privacy Policy and Legal Notice in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: Allegiance–A New Musical (www.allegiancemusical.com) (this “website”). All references to “we” or “us” in this Privacy Policy and Legal Notice refers to Allegiance Broadway LLC or its managers, predecessors or successors, the production company responsible for producing “Allegiance–A New Musical”.

### Information Collected and How We Use It

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer this website. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information, such as country of origin and similar information.

This website also may use unique identifiers to confirm data, such as your geographical location, and we use such data in the aggregate to run internal analyses to improve upon your user experience.

Through surveys and newsletter registration, this website may request users to give us contact, demographic, and/or general financial information (such as their name, locale, gender, age, income level and email address). The demographic information is used to enhance user experience so we can be more content specific. The contact information is used to notify users of new content, for surveys and newsletters, via email. Financial information related to income level that is collected is used primari for in-house statistics, advertising, and marketing target information. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

In addition, we may employ outside agents, meaning other companies or individuals to perform functions on our behalf, such as sending postal mail and e-mail, conducting sweepstakes and other promotional activities, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments and providing customer service. These agents have access to personal information needed to perform their functions. Other than such outside agents, suppliers and vendors, we keep all of your personal information private and will not share it with any third party, unless you have authorized us to or we are legally required to do so. We may also release personal information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of ourselves, our clients, our users, or others. Of course, we may disclose any personal information about you to law enforcement, other government officials, or other third parties, as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us to legal liability.

### Contests

We may run contests on this website in which we ask visitors for contact information (such as their name, address and/or email address) and demographic information (such as their zip code, age, and/or income level). The user’s contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary, such as if they win a contest or to notify users of upcoming contests.

We generally would host our own contest or sweepstakes and, in such instance, all information that is collected by us would be used only by us subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and Legal Notice or as otherwise provided in any applicable contest or sweepstakes rules.  In certain instances, a third party may host the contest or sweepstakes and all collected information would then be shared with us and that third party and otherwise used by us subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and Legal Notice or as otherwise provided in any applicable contest or sweepstakes rules.

In connection with the contests, we may also share contact information with third parties for shipping and prize fulfillment purposes. In our contest registration, we give visitors the opportunity to sign up for this website’s newsletter. However, visitors may opt-out of receiving future mailings by selecting the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of the newsletter.

### Interactive Programs

We may run interactive programs on this website such as games, group events, promotions, and fan club activities in which we ask visitors for contact information similar to what we ask for in contests.  As with contests, the information is used to contest the program participants when necessary.  We may hold our own programs or elect to utilize a third party to host the program, in which case all information would then be share by us and that third party.  As with contests, visitors may elect to opt-out of receiving our mailings or newsletters.

Users that this website knows to be under the age of 13 are hereby required to provide the e-mail address of their parent or guardian to the Administrator (privacy@allegiancemusical.com) so that this website may alert the parent or guardian of their child’s use of this website. The parent or guardian must consent to this website’s collection of their child’s personal information. A known child user will be restricted from providing personal information until such consent is received. No information collected from users known to be under age 13 will be used for any marketing or promotional purposes outside this website. If this website collects personally identifiable information from children, it will do so in compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (U.S.C. 6501 et seq.). Links to Other Sites This website may contain links to other websites. This website is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites.

### Public Forums

At times, this website may contain message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. We request users to give us contact information, such as name, email, address, occupation, and interests to be a registered bulletin board user. This information is optional and not necessary to post messages. This information may be used by the administrator to send the user email notices. However, users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and users should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information.

### Security

This website has commercially reasonable security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

### Choice/Opt-Out

This website provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This website gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.

Users can send email to: [privacy@allegiancemusical.com](mailto:privacy@allegiancemusical.com?subject=Privacy%20Opt-Out&body=To%20Whom%20It%20May%20Concern%2C%0A%0AI%27d%20like%20to%20op-out%20of%20any%20communication%20via%20email%20sent%20by%20your%20company.%20Please%20remove%20my%20email%20address%20from%20your%20distribution%20list.)

Users can send mail to the following postal address:

Allegiance Broadway, Limited Liability Company  
1560 Broadway, Suite 700  
New York, NY 10036

Users can call the following telephone number: 212-944-6586

### Use of Third Party Ad Networks

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is anonymous.

### Correct/Update

This website gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.

Users can send email to: [privacy@allegiancemusical.com](mailto:privacy@allegiancemusical.com?subject=Privacy%20Correction&body=To%20Whom%20It%20May%20Concern%2C%0A%0AI%27d%20like%20to%20update%20some%20of%20the%20information%20you%20are%20currently%20maintaining%2C%20which%20I%20previously%20provided%3A%0A)

Users can send mail to the following postal address:

Allegiance Broadway, Limited Liability Company  
1560 Broadway, Suite 700  
New York, NY 10036

Users can call the following telephone number: 917-720-3289

### Copyright Notice

All text, images, graphics, sounds and software code (“Content”) on this website are copyrighted property of its respective owners, its clients, contributors and its programmers unless otherwise noted. They may only be used for the personal education of site visitors. They may not be placed in the public domain. You may not reproduce, redistribute, publish or otherwise use by electronic or any other means any of the Content without the prior written consent.

### Trademarks

“Allegiance” and other trademarks, service marks, brands, product names, designs and logos related to “Allegiance’” and indicated on this website are owned, controlled or licensed by us or our designated agents, or by the rights holders of the theatrical work “Allegiance.” They may not be used or displayed without our prior written consent. All other trademarks, service marks, brands, product names, designs, company names and logos appearing on this website are the property of their respective owners.

### Applicable Law

These terms will be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of New York, without regard to any principles of conflicts of law. You agree that any action at law or in equity that arises out of or relates to any use of this website will be filed only in the state or federal courts located in New York County, and you hereby consent and submit to the personal jurisdiction of such courts for the purposes of litigating any such action. Successors In the event that we are, or any component of our operations is, merged with, or is acquired by, another entity, then any such successor or acquiring entity may become the successor to our obligations with respect to the personal information that you have provided to us, which would be necessary for the entity to effectively continue our business. By using this website, you consent to any such use of such personal information by such an entity assuming control of our operations as a result of a merger, purchase of assets, or liquidation in bankruptcy or insolvency.

### Your Acceptance of These Terms

By visiting this website, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy and Legal Notice and to the collection and use of this information by us. We will always fully disclose our privacy policies, and we will promptly post any changes to our policy on this page.

You agree that we may retain and use your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy and legal Notice until you inform us in writing that you do not agree with this Privacy Policy and Legal Notice and agree that you will not use this website for a reasonable period of time thereafter. By using this website after we post any changes to this Privacy Policy and Legal Notice, you agree to accept those changes. If you choose to visit this website, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and Legal Notice.

### Contacting the Website

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy and Legal Notice, the practices of this website, or your dealings with this website, you can send an email to [privacy@allegiancemusical.com](mailto:privacy@allegiancemusical.com?subject=Privacy%20Question).
